<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on GentleR Blog</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on GentleR Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>First GentleR Session</title>
      <link>/2019/02/19/first-gentler-session/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/02/19/first-gentler-session/</guid>
      <description>What a fantastic start to GentleR! We had a room full of over 20 R enthusiasts from long-term users through to newcomers wanting to know more. We had representation across so many levels and fields, from PhD students to Professors, and from Spatial Sciences, Biology and Ecology to Chemical Engineering, Economics and even Maths and Stats! While everyone in the room professed to knowing how to do linear regression in R, only about a quarter of us had written packages and/or built shiny apps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to write a blog post</title>
      <link>/2019/01/30/how-to-write-a-blog-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/01/30/how-to-write-a-blog-post/</guid>
      <description>Hi Everyone,
As you can (possibly) see, this blog has been created using blogdown. Blogdown is an R package that, Rmarkdown style, takes your info and creates a blog with them! Cool huh? So, as a complete newby to this wonderful bit of awesome, I’m going to write down the steps you need to write a post for this blog!… Possibly so I can remind myself how to do it later… but also so that you can see some steps if you’d like to try and write your own!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to GentleR</title>
      <link>/2019/01/30/welcome-to-gentler/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/01/30/welcome-to-gentler/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to GentleR! The place where no question is too silly, no problem is too large and no language other than R will do!
We are a group of statisticians and researchers who meet every week, for one golden hour, to discuss all things R, statistics and research in general. Everyone is welcome to attend and the goal is to workshop through issues that people are having with R or statistics in a friendly, informative and non-judgmental way.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>